export const User = [
    {
      id: "1",
      photo:"https://openclipart.org/download/181856/1376606916.svg" ,
      username: "shashi",
      password: "852183",
      email: "shashi.raj213@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/287493/Cartoonboy.svg",
      username: "shourav",
      password: "763294",
      email: "shourav@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/287459/teenboy.svg",
      username: "shubham",
      password: "950457",
      email: "shubham@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/233320/Michelle-Trachtenberg-1-by-Rones.svg",
      username: "puja",
      password: "886307",
      email: "puja@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/276444/GlassesMan.svg",
      username: "aditya",
      password: "732385",
      email: "aditya@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/227463/Flat-Shaded-Male-Avatar-4.svg",
      username: "binay",
      password: "900671",
      email: "binay@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/317567/1553889167.svg",
      username: "jayshree",
      password: "721946",
      email: "jayshree@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/337743/young-man.svg",
      username: "rajeev",
      password: "930489",
      email: "rajeev@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/338694/cowboymanhead.svg",
      username: "rohit",
      password: "821047",
      email: "rohit@example.com",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      photo: "https://openclipart.org/download/213096/greeter1-4.svg",
      username: "santosh",
      password: "947227",
      email: "santosh@example.com",
    },
  ];
  
  export const Q_A_ = [
    {
      id: "1",
      answeredBy: "sushil kumar",
      questionedBy: "aman gupta",
      question: "What is web designing?",
      answer: "Web design refers to the process of creating the visual layout and look of a website so that they resonate with a company's brand, convey information, and support user-friendliness.",
    },
    {
      id: "2",
      answeredBy: "gaurav anand",
      questionedBy: "ranveer kapoor",
      question: "What is computer software?",
      answer: "Information architecture (IA) refers to the process of planning, organizing, structuring, and labeling content in a comprehensive, logical, and sustainable manner.",
    },
    {
      id: "3",
      answeredBy: "hemant kumar",
      questionedBy: "utakarsh anand",
      question: "What is software engineering?",
      answer: "Software engineering is an engineering branch associated with software system development.",
    },
    {
      id: "4",
      answeredBy: "sanju kumar",
      questionedBy: "sunny sujaan",
      question: "What is your secret of writing good answers?",
      answer: "Secret actually there is no secret in writing good answer. I just talk about the things which is biased to a certain amount of people.",
    },
    {
      id: "5",
      answeredBy: "tarun kumar",
      questionedBy: "sujeet kumar",
      question: "Which is the first satellite launch by India?",
      answer: "Aryabhata was the first artificial satellite launched by India on 19th April 1975.",
    },
    {
      id: "6",
      answeredBy: "abhishek anand",
      questionedBy: "vivek kumar",
      question: "Who is founder of Hotmail?",
      answer: "Sabeer Bhatia (born 30 December 1968) is an Indian businessman who co-founded the first free web-based email service, Hotmail.com in 1996.",
    },
    {
      id: "7",
      answeredBy: "naveen parkar",
      questionedBy: "jeevan jyoti",
      question: "What is website designing?",
      answer: "Website designing is mostly about developing a website using different tools and designers as per the requirements, and these designing can be done as per the significance.",
    },
    {
      id: "8",
      answeredBy: "rohan gupta",
      questionedBy: "sushant kumar",
      question: "What is full stack web development?",
      answer: "Full stack development is the process of designing, creating, testing, and deploying a complete web application from start to finish.",
    },
    {
      id: "9",
      answeredBy: "madhukar anand",
      questionedBy: "vikaram singh",
      question: "What is the role of developer??",
      answer: "Developers, also known as software developers or computer programmers, are responsible for developing, coding, installing, and maintaining software systems.",
    },
    {
      id: "10",
      answeredBy: "rahul verma",
      questionedBy: "shishu ranjan",
      question: "What is a processor?",
      answer: "A processor is an integrated electronic circuit that performs the calculations that run a computer.",
    },
  ];